

Enise Kizilaslan

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

CONTACT



(4) +49 (0)172 375 1464



enisekizilaslan@gmail.com



https://enisekizilaslan.netlify.app/

ABOUT ME

I am a front-end developer based in Hannover, Germany.

I have completed my Advanced Responsive Web Development and Advanced React Development degrees from SheCodes Coding School and received my Front-End Developer Diploma. During this degree program, I gained valuable front-end developer experience through building countless apps, portfolio/marketing projects, landing pages, search engines and

I also have mathematics and education backgrounds as a teacher and college counselor with a Master's degree in Education. I am an American citizen and have residency and work permit also in Europe as I am currently residing in Germany.

SKILLS

HTML + CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, React JS, Vue JS, Node, NPM, SEO, Responsive, VS Code, API, Axios, GitHub, Hosting, Flexbox

LANGUAGES

English - Fluent

Turkish - Fluent

German - Pre-Intermediate

REFERENCES

Available upon request.

EDUCATION

SheCodes Coding School

Front-end Development 2022/2023

University of California San Diego

College Counseling 2015/2016

Central Michigan University

Master of Arts in Education 2010/2013

Erciyes University

Mathematics Education - major Science Education - minor 2002/2006

WORK EXPERIENCE

College Counselor at Michigan Math and Science Academy 2015 - 2017 Mathematics Teacher (Volunteer) at Michigan Math and Science Academy 2010 - 2011 Mathematics Teacher at Panayir Elementary School

2006 - 2007

PROJECTS

Weather App Project - HTML, CSS, React JS, API, Axios https://weather-app-jsreact.netlify.app/

Dictionary Project - HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, React JS, API, Axios https://dictionary-app-project.netlify.app/

Homestore Marketing Project - HTML, CSS, JavaScript https://npc44k.csb.app/

Travel Project - HTML, CSS, Figma Design, Flexbox https://istanbul-travel-project.netlify.app/

World Clock Project - HTML - CSS - JavaScript, API https://world-clock-site.netlify.app/